cachedpages.com 2019-10-18

# Cached Pages - Get the cached page of any URL

At CachedPages.com we recognize that privacy is important. We offer a service that does not require you to register for an account or provide any personal information to us. However, we may collect the following types of information:

  * **CachedPages.com cookies:** When you visit CachedPages.com, we send one or more cookies (a small file containing a string of characters) to your computer that uniquely identifies your web browser. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service by storing user preferences and tracking user trends, such as how people search. Most web browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features and services at CachedPages.com may not function properly if your browser's cookies are disabled. 

  * **Web log information:** When you use CachedPages.com services, our servers automatically record information that your web browser sends whenever you visit a web site. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser type, browser language, browser plug-ins, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. 

  * **User communications:** When you send email or other communication to CachedPages.com, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services. 

  * **Affiliated web sites:** We offer some of our services in connection with other web sites. Personal information that you provide to those web sites may be sent to CachedPages.com in order to deliver the service. We process such information in accordance with this Policy. The affiliated sites may have different privacy practices and we encourage you to read their privacy policies. 

  * **Web links:** CachedPages.com may present links in a format that enables us to keep track of whether these links have been followed. We use this information to improve the quality of our search services and web site content. 

  * **Other web sites:** This Privacy Policy applies to services offered by CachedPages.com. We do not exercise control over the sites displayed as search results or links from within our various services. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. 

CachedPages.com only processes personal information for the purposes described in the applicable Privacy Policy and/or privacy notice for specific services. In addition to the above, such purposes include:

  * Providing our products and services to users, including the display of customized content and advertising.
  * Auditing, research and analysis in order to maintain, protect and improve our services.
  * Ensuring the technical functioning of our web site and the services it provides.
  * Developing new services.

**Information sharing**

CachedPages.com only shares personal information with other companies or individuals outside of CachedPages.com in the following limited circumstances:

We may share with third parties certain pieces of aggregated, non-personal information, such as the number of users who searched for a particular term, for example, or how many users clicked on a particular advertisement. Such information does not identify you individually.

However, these third parties may place and read cookies on your browser, or may use web beacons to collect information, in the course of displaying certain parts of CachedPages.com pages.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit CachedPages.com. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this website and to other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

Google, as a third party advertising vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our website. In this respect, please note the following:

  * Google's use of the [DoubleClick DART cookie](https://support.google.com/adsense/answer/2839090?hl=en) enables it to serve ads to our website users based on their visit to our website and other websites on the Internet. 
  * You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/). 

Cached Pages Home
